# Amanda Migala

#### **Contact**

- Email Megoes to -->amanda.migala@gprep.com
- (509) 828-7742
- My Websitegoes to -->https://amandarmigala.netlify.app
- Spokane, WA

#### Social Media

<u>LinkedIngoes to -->www.linkedin.com/in/amigala</u> <u>GitHubgoes to -->https://github.com/amigala</u>

# Biography

Hi my name is Amanda Migala and I am a VCD design major, and I am also gaining my certification for User Experience at Eastern Washington University. I grew up being more on the creative side rather then the logical side and loved to come with things that I imagined though drawing, photography, and story telling. When I graduated high school, I remember my drama teacher mentioning to me how I was a quiet genius who embraced so much creativity during my years in school and hoped I would continue that during college. From then on, I decided to persure design as my major not just because of the creative part of it but also to gain skills in problem solving that could impact others I work with. I tend have an open minded when I try new things. I love trying to be outside especially in the summer and go biking, hiking, or swimming.

# Experience

# Apple Inc., Spokane, WA — Operations Specialist

July 2022 -- Present

Continuing my time at Apple, I worked my way to be transferred into a new role at Apple as an Operations Specialist. In my role, I was able to continue to develop my current skills along with some new vital skills like attention to details and ability to adapt to change. At Apple, I was tasked to complete daily inventory operations which are receiving, counting, returning, and running tasks. In addition, I also completed other inventory tasks to align with Apple's visual standards. During my time in this role, I was able to collaborate with my team on inventory procedures and keep up to date on inventory process changes and training resources. I was also given the opportunity to develop my leadership skills with other teammates to help their own growth and development at Apple.

#### Apple Inc., Spokane, WA — Product Zone Specialist

Sept 2021 -- July 2022

During my time at Apple, I had started off as a seasonal employee as a product zone specialist, and worked my way to become a permanent specialist and have been in my permanent role since March 2022. In my role, I have been able to develop vital skills like strong communication skills, creative problem solving, excellent customer experience, and providing support for my teammates. At Apple, I was tasked to assist in customer experience by learning about their needs' and matching them to the right product. During my time at Apple, I believe I have not only been able to help consumers find the right product for them to be successful within their passions but also be able to collaborate with my team on any kind of support they need within the product zone.

#### **Education**

### Eastern Washington University, Cheney, WA — Bachelor's Degree

2019 -- 2023

- Major: Visual Communication Design
- Certification: User Experience
- Graduation: June 2023
- GPA 3.5

### Skills

- Excellent Communication
- Reliable
- Quick Learner
- Creativity

## **Awards**

- Washington State Opportunity Scholarship
- Eastern Washington's Honors Scholarship